<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 0x738</title>
    <link>https://sjdh.us/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 0x738</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:55:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sjdh.us/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Thoughts on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://sjdh.us/posts/social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 19:55:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjdh.us/posts/social-media/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen what seems like a rise in people who are taking breaks or alltogether leaving social media platforms for one reason or another. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been fond of it either - I use Reddit and Snapchat exclusively - but I&amp;rsquo;ve never taken the time to lay out some thoughts on why. I figured this would be a good start to expanding the variety of content on my page here, so lets get into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updates</title>
      <link>https://sjdh.us/posts/updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:59:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjdh.us/posts/updates/</guid>
      <description>The spring semester has officialy ended for me, and I&amp;rsquo;ve recently begun the process of relocating to attend my universities main campus for the rest of my undergrad degree. While I&amp;rsquo;ll be quiet for most of this summer (and I&amp;rsquo;m sure a bit into the fall), I do plan to expand the scope of this blog as well as write more. I think of this as more of a personal journal, rather than a fully technical oriented blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Zig for ARM Development</title>
      <link>https://sjdh.us/posts/continuing-with-zig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 18:30:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sjdh.us/posts/continuing-with-zig/</guid>
      <description>I recently decided to move my toy RPI3 kernel over to Zig from Rust. I decided to do this both for some technical reasons, as well as some personal reasons. In the process of doing said transistion, I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be a good idea to collect my thoughts and reasons on why I chose to move and make them avaiable here. So without further ado, here they are:
Binary Size Compared to other embedded environments, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to be nearly as concerned about binary size on the RPI3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>